Is that a sword?
It has to be
at least 300 years old, right?
You're right.
Isn't this bad? What should we do?
-I can't contain my excitement!
-Me neither!
Tanjiro, you didn't get
your newly forged sword, right?
Maybe you should take it?
No, no, no! I can't take it!
Steel from the Sengoku period
is high quality!
Don't talk me into taking it!
We found it because you shattered it.
Just because it had been damaged
many times already.
It just happened to break
while I was training with it.
Are you sure you won't take it?
Want to try pulling it out?
Yeah, I want to see the sword!
It's rusty.
Well, it's only natural.
Given no one knew about it,
no one took care of it
for three centuries.
Sorry to dash your hopes.
It's okay. I don't mind.
Tanjiro!
Tanjiro, I'm really sorry!
What's that?
Demon Slayer: Swordsmith Village Arc
Episode 3:
A Sword from Over 300 Years Ago
Wait, who is it? Is that you, Haganezuka?
I heard everything.
Leave it to me.
Leave what to you?
What are you doing?
Leave it to me.
Please, let go of it!
Why are you trying to take it away?
Shut up and leave it to me!
Why do you show up out of the blue
and tell us to leave it to you?
Just leave it to me!
No! This is Kotetsu's!
Leave it to me!
I came here to see you.
Where have you been?
If I say leave it to me,
just leave it to me!
Leave what to you? Explain yourself!
I said leave it to me!
An adult shouldn't act like that!
Boys, Haganezuka's weak spot is his sides.
Right here.
Tickle, tickle.
Kanamori. Long time no see.
Hello, Tanjiro.
Haganezuka will be exhausted for a while
after being tickled.
So let me explain it to you.
Please, forgive Haganezuka.
Well, he was secluding himself
in the mountains for training.
Training?
Yes. In order to be able to make
a stronger sword so you won't die.
He won't be honest about it, though.
For me?
You've entrusted him
to make you a sword, right?
I think he was happy about that.
He was often out of charge
because the swordsmen detest him.
Is that so?
He sucks at socializing, you know.
That's why he hasn't gotten married yet.
He's back.
I will take this rusty sword
and polish it using the Nichirin Sword
polishing art of the Haganezuka family.
Then why not just say so from the start?
All you said was, "Leave it to me!"
even though we don't know other.
Like an idiot
who can only remember one thing.
What did you say? Say it again!
You're choking me…
His sides! His sides! Aim at his sides!
While I'm taking care of this one,
use this sword instead.
Thank you.
That's what happened yesterday.
Apparently, it'll take three days
and three nights to polish that sword.
So he'll finish it the day after tomorrow.
I'm worried
because it said the polishing method
is so harsh that people have gotten killed
as a result.
But he forbade me from peeking.
Do you think I can take a look?
I don't give a shit! Get out!
Don't talk to me like I'm your friend!
Huh? We aren't friends?
Of course not!
You broke my arm, remember?
Don't tell me you forgot.
Genya, it was your own fault
for hitting that girl.
I had to.
Don't call me by my first name!
These rice crackers are delicious.
Do you want one?
No, shit!
I don't want it! Get lost!
Wasn't your front tooth missing
at the hot spring?
You must be mistaken.
I know I'm not mistaken.
I still have it, here.
Why did you keep it?
You're freaking disgusting!
Well, you dropped it,
so I wanted to return it.
Are you out of your mind? Throw it away!
Get the hell out!
Like this, this, and then like this.
Next, this way.
Why is Genya always so angry?
I wonder if he's still hungry.
I think I'll invite Genya
to have a meal tomorrow morning.
You think it's a good idea, Nezuko?
We've had a bath together,
so we should have a meal together next.
I'd like to get to know Genya better.
Braiding is difficult.
Now you have the same hairstyle
as Kanroji.
Nezuko, the moon looks beautiful tonight.
I was in the bath for too long.
I have to work early in the morning.
A vase?
I didn't see this when I was going up.
Who put a vase out here?
It could be dangerous, you know.
What a horrible flavor!
The flesh of mountain swordsmiths
is simply not good for eating.
But that's all right.
Still, destroying this place
will certainly weaken the demon hunters.
Must hurry. Must hurry.
Thanks to Gyokko, we found the village.
But our lord is furious.
Hurry. Hurry.
We must kill everyone…
Everyone who opposes our lord.
Old man, have you finished it?
No one's here.
Big bro…
I have to do it.
Do you know a swordsmith named Kanamori?
Tokito! What are you doing here?
Wait, did you just pinch my nose?
Yes, I did.
Your reaction was too slow.
Come on, I would be able to tell
if you were a bad guy.
Fair enough. If I was a bad guy,
I wouldn't pinch your nose.
Yeah, I know Kanamori. But why?
Perhaps he's with Haganezuka.
Kanamori is my new swordsmith.
Where is Haganezuka?
Shall we look for him together?
Why do you care about people so much?
Don't you have other concerns?
Because helping others eventually
ends up being good for me.
I was thinking of going too.
You came at the right time.
What? What did you just say?
Your words earlier…
Huh? I said you came at the right time.
Ow!
Nezuko, you're awake.
It hurts…
Let's go to Haganezuka's together.
That girl is a strange creature.
Huh? Is she strange?
Yeah. She's very strange.
How can I say it?
I can't put it into words.
Have I met her before?
Was she already like this?
I wonder…
Is someone here?
Yes, someone's here.
Wait, what? Is it a demon?
How did this demon get here?
I didn't notice it until now.
This demon is definitely an Upper Rank!
Mist Breathing,
Fourth Form: Shifting Flow Slash.
It's fast. I didn't kill it.
Please, stop. Don't attack me.
It hurts!
Don't hesitate!
It's a demon that's killed many people.
Otherwise, it wouldn't be able
to dodge a Hashira's attack.
Hinokami Kagura:
Sunflower Thrust!
Did I get it?
Why doesn't it counterattack?
Isn't it an Upper Rank?
Nezuko, don't use that form!
Turn back or it will trigger
your demonification!
You cut me!
He severed its head.
That was fast, but…
Beheading Upper Ranks
doesn't mean killing them.
Tokito, stay alert!
He split in two!
One grew a head and the other grew a body.
I'll get the one in the back!
As long as we cut at the same time…
Nezuko!
Tokito!
It's really fun!
That little bean went flying so far.
Didn't it, Sekido?
There's nothing fun about it.
I'm just so angry.
I'm also angry about being
mixed in with you, Karaku.
PLEASURE
Is that so?
Aren't you glad we've separated?
Do their heads need to be cut off
at the same time too?
What is this?
That khakkhara…
Crap. I'm about to lose consciousness.
Someone's on the roof?
Genya?
What is that weapon? Is that a gun?
It smells just like Nichirin Swords.
One of them is still standing.
This is fun. How interesting.
I've never felt an attack
like that before.
Genya! No!
No matter how strong your weapons are,
this demon…
can't be defeated!
They will split every time you kill them!
Then rejuvenate and get stronger!
They're just letting you
cut their heads off!
This demon doesn't care
about having its head cut off.
That means its head's not its weak spot.
Now they have four bodies.
It regenerates so fast.
Isn't there any pattern?
Where does it regenerate fastest?
It must have a weak spot.
Find it! Look for it!
There must be something.
Shouldn't there be four bodies?
What a delightful moment!
It's been a long time since I split up!
This one can fly.
Each of them has different abilities.
Nezuko! Don't worry about me!
Just help Genya--
UPPER - FOUR
You're so weak it's sad.
Genya!
Nezuko, help him!
Help Genya! Please, hurry!
You have the time
to worry about others, huh?
Hinokami Kagura!
He's good. This is quite delightful.
DELIGHT
Grab onto a branch! A branch!
Hurry! Stand up! Get on your feet!
The villagers are in danger.
I have to protect them.
Crap! My body is numb.
I can't hear anything.
I've been blown away quite far.
Must get back as fast as possible.
A demon and a child.
A child must be inexperienced
in swordsmithing skills.
Helping him is low-priority.
From the looks of it,
that's not the main body
but created by some demon arts.
There's no reason to stop here.
If the entire village is under attack,
the number one priority is the chief.
I have to protect those who have
the greatest skills and abilities.
What I need to do now is to eliminate
the Upper Rank demon
and protect the village.
Saving an inexperienced swordsmith won't…
Because helping others eventually
ends up being good for me.
Run.
You…
You'll just get in my way,
so get out of here, will you?
DEMON SLAYER: SWORDSMITH VILLAGE ARC
NO. 3
We're all being attacked by demons
while Haganezuka's polishing your sword.
-Are you okay?
-Yup.
He even made this sword.
But he never changes.
Yeah, his nature will never change.
Now it's time for the Taishō era secret.
Haganezuka attaches wind chimes
to his woven hat because he loves it.
When he was a child,
every time he threw a tantrum,
the adults around him
would ring the wind chimes.
CHIEF TECCHIN'S FACE
You learn something new every day.
This is for you.
If you think that's going to put me
in a good mood, you're wrong!
Ring! Ring! Ring!
Don't treat me like a child!
Next up on Episode 4: "Thank You, Tokito."
Have you calmed down?
Like I said, don't treat me like a--
Ring! Ring! Ring!
TO BE CONTINUED